<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
    xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">

    <ui:with field="res" type="com.arcbees.hive.client.resources.Resources" />

    <ui:style>
        .sectionText {
          margin-left: 176px;
          text-align: justify;
        }
        
        .imgFloatLeft {
          float: left;
          margin-left: 15px;
        }
        
        .section {
          position: relative;
          width: 804px;
          margin-left: 61px;
          margin-top: 41px;
          margin-bottom: 41px;
          min-height: 300px;
        }
        
        .marginBottom {
          margin-bottom: 35px;
        }
        
        .miel {
          margin-left: 191px;
          margin-bottom: 15px;
        }
    </ui:style>

    <g:HTMLPanel styleName="{res.style.blogBackground}">
        <div class="{res.style.blogLeftFull}" />
        <div class="{res.style.blogRightFull}" />

        <div class="{style.section}">
            <g:Image resource="{res.serConsultation}" styleName="{style.imgFloatLeft}" />

            <div class="{style.sectionText} {style.marginBottom}">
                <h2>Consulting</h2>
                <p>Our consulting services help you improve the quality of your applications and
                the performance of your development team. A qualified member of ArcBees will join
                your team to help you with your specific need, be it software development, software
                design, tooling, or process and methodology. Our consultant will be easily
                accessible to work with your team and respond to all your questions.</p>
            </div>

            <g:Image resource="{res.serDeveloppement}"
                styleName="{style.imgFloatLeft}" />

            <div class="{style.sectionText} {style.marginBottom}">
                <h2>Development</h2>
                <p>ArcBees has the resources to bring your project to life. We gather your
                requirements, put a team together, and work hand in hand throughout the project.
                Depending on your needs we can provide a complete development team or cover only 
                some aspects of the development cycle. Our expertise with cutting edge technologies
                and our position as community leaders on good development practices ensure that
                your future application will exceed your expectations in terms of quality,
                maintainability and ease-of-use.</p>
            </div>

            <g:Image resource="{res.serFormation}" styleName="{style.imgFloatLeft}" />

            <div class="{style.sectionText} {style.marginBottom}">
                <h2>Training</h2>
                <p>ArcBees can help you hit the ground running with our products and related
                technologies. Our team of expert communicators have been invited to renowned
                conferences around the world, including Google I/O. Their personalized training
                sessions will deepen your staff understanding of GWT, GWT-Platform, AppEngine and
                related technologies. We also offer hands-on seminar on these technologies, as well
                as training with tools and processes that will ensure your development team reaches
                its full potential. Wide-ranging introductory classes are also available.</p>
            </div>

            <g:Image resource="{res.serSupport}" styleName="{style.imgFloatLeft}" />

            <div class="{style.sectionText}">
                <h2>Support</h2>
                <p>ArcBees technical support is here for you should you need quick response time to
                your critical business application. Our support plans focus on ArcBees products and
                related technologies, such as GWT and AppEngine. Here are our packages:</p>
            </div>

            <g:Image resource="{res.serMiel}" styleName="{style.miel}" />
        </div>

        <div class="{res.style.blogDown}" />
        <div class="{res.style.sloganCoinGauche}" />
        <div class="{res.style.sloganCoinDroit}" />
    </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>