<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
             xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">

    <ui:with field="res" type="com.arcbees.hive.client.resource.Resources"/>

    <ui:style>
        .sectionText {
            margin-left: 176px;
            text-align: justify;
        }

        .imgFloatLeft {
            float: left;
            margin-left: 15px;
        }

        .section {
            position: relative;
            width: 804px;
            margin-left: 61px;
            margin-top: 41px;
            margin-bottom: 41px;
            min-height: 300px;
        }

        .textAlignRight {
            text-align: right;
        }

        .marginBottom {
            margin-bottom: 35px;
        }
    </ui:style>

    <g:HTMLPanel styleName="{res.style.blogBackground}">
        <div class="{res.style.blogLeftFull}"/>
        <div class="{res.style.blogRightFull}"/>

        <div class="{style.section}">
            <g:Image resource="{res.productGWTP}" styleName="{style.imgFloatLeft}"/>

            <div class="{style.sectionText} {style.marginBottom}">
                <p>
                    <strong>GWT-Platform (GWTP) is the most popular Model-View-Presenter framework
                        for the Google Web Toolkit, ensuring your GWT application will be built
                        according to the best practices of the industry.
                    </strong>
                    GWTP speeds up the development of Web applications and is particularly useful to
                    ensure the quality and maintainability of large-scale webapps. This open source
                    framework, introduced by ArcBees in early 2010, has known rapid growth thanks
                    to its widespread adoption. Its situation as the number one MVP framework for
                    GWT has led to ArcBees being invited to present it at the prestigions Google I/O
                    conference in 2011. GWT-Platform is composed of different modules including the
                    MVP framework itself, a command pattern module, a service to make modern webapps
                    crawlable by search engines, and tools to help with various facets of GWT
                    project developement.
                </p>

                <p class="{style.textAlignRight}">
                    <a href="http://www.gwtplatform.com/">GWT-Platform's development web site</a>
                    <br/>
                    <a
                            href="http://code.google.com/p/gwt-platform/wiki/GettingStarted?tm=6">GWT-Platform's
                        documentation
                    </a>
                    <br/>
                    <a
                            href="https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/gwt-platform">GWT-Platform's mailing list
                    </a>
                </p>
            </div>

            <g:Image resource="{res.productJUKITO}" styleName="{style.imgFloatLeft}"/>

            <div class="{style.sectionText}">
                <p>
                    <strong>Jukito complements your testing infrastructure by letting you rely on
                        the power of dependency injection directly in your tests.
                    </strong>
                    Jukito's
                    auto-mocking mechanism will dramatically reduce the size of your test classes,
                    leading to tests that are both more reasable and easier to maintain. Jukito is
                    a very light-weight addition to your testing infrastructure and its use can
                    easily be combined with other testing technologies. It is therefore easy to
                    adopt Jukito midway through a project, letting you gradually simplify your
                    testing code.
                </p>

                <p class="{style.textAlignRight}">
                    <a href="http://www.jukito.org/">Jukito's development web site</a>
                    <br/>
                    <a
                            href="http://code.google.com/p/jukito/wiki/GettingStarted?tm=6">Jukito's documentation
                    </a>
                    <br/>
                    <a href="https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/jukito">Jukito's mailing list</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>

        <div class="{res.style.blogDown}"/>
    </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>
