<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui='urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder'
             xmlns:g='urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui'
             ui:generateFormat='com.google.gwt.i18n.rebind.format.PropertiesFormat'
             ui:generateKeys="com.google.gwt.i18n.rebind.keygen.MD5KeyGenerator"
             ui:generateLocales="en">
    <ui:with field="res" type="com.arcbees.hive.client.resource.Resources"/>
    <g:HTMLPanel addStyleNames="{res.style.mainSection} {res.style.bulleBgMain} {res.style.cornerBottom}">
        <p>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > introduction paragraph">ArcBees is a business partner of Google, the search
                engine most used worldwide to find information on the
                Internet. ArcBees is then one of the companies best placed to offer you the visibility you need.
                However,
                certain standards must be met. And these standards are based on the user experience (UX). Click the
                orange
                circles to find benefits.
            </ui:msg>
        </p>

        <h2>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Mobile website and mobile application > Title">Mobile website and mobile
                application
            </ui:msg>
        </h2>

        <p>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Mobile website and mobile application > Paragraph">ArcBees has expertise in
                design mobile of website such as iPhone, Androïde, BlackBerry and Windows.
                We can
                program, develop and design this mobile website in compatibility of social marketing like facebook and
                others.
                This approach is created to optimize the use and promote the development of your social networks.
            </ui:msg>
        </p>

        <h2>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Information design > Title">Information design</ui:msg>
        </h2>

        <p>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Information design > Paragraph">ArcBees is able to do the thorough,
                user-centered facilitating access to information. This study
                facilitates
                understanding of not just informations, but also the interface design which makes it more intuitive for
                good
                numbers of users, as they must be guided through the pages and content without the need to a research
                effort.
            </ui:msg>
        </p>

        <h2>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Information architecture > Title">Information architecture</ui:msg>
        </h2>

        <p>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Information architecture > Paragraph">The information architecture is an
                organizing structure, navigation, terminology and search
                functions to
                build
                and establish a system of content. The objective is to find a system for organizing information that is
                relevant
                to optimal research tasks for the user. The problems are not the same depending on the objectives and
                scope
                of
                the application or website.
            </ui:msg>

        </p>

        <h2>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Interaction design / interface > Title">Interaction design / interface
            </ui:msg>
        </h2>

        <p>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Interaction design / interface > Paragraph">ArcBees offers an interaction
                design phase of observation and analysis to identify pathways relevant
                for your
                website or application software. So, your application reflects the needs of the user and your target
                audience.
                In this way, the user is guided through by interface so intuitive.
            </ui:msg>
        </p>

        <h2>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Ergonomic design > Title">Ergonomic design</ui:msg>
        </h2>

        <p>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Ergonomic design > Paragraph">ArcBees wonders about the intentions and
                navigation patterns of users. By having this creative
                process, we
                improve your conversion rate of your website and your income. We define a user profil, use personas,
                orient
                the
                purchase, improve the user experience, ergonomics adapt the application to the mobile format.
            </ui:msg>
        </p>

        <h2>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Performance measures > Title">Performance measures</ui:msg>
        </h2>

        <p>
            <ui:msg description="Ux Design > Performance measures > Paragraph">Arcbees offers opportunities to assess
                your performance. Our methodology is based on iterative
                processes of
                creation: continuous improvement (which allow you to track transactions that have affected, validated,
                issued
                and stopped), your performance and calculate their impact on your investments in the web.
            </ui:msg>
        </p>
    </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>
