<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
             xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">

    <ui:with field="res" type="com.arcbees.hive.client.resources.Resources"/>

    <ui:style>
        .sectionText {
            text-align: justify;
            margin-left: 51px;
            margin-right: 51px;
        }

        .imgFloatRight {
            float: right;
            margin-right: 41px;
        }

        .section {
            width: 888px;
        }

        .topH2 {
            margin-top: 0;
        }
    </ui:style>

    <g:HTMLPanel>
        <div class="{style.section}">
            <g:Image resource="{res.blogBookedin}" styleName="{style.imgFloatRight}"/>

            <div class="{style.sectionText}">
                <h2 class="{style.topH2}">BookedIN</h2>

                <p>
                    <strong>Web site:</strong>
                    <a href="http://www.coldwin.com/" target="_blank">
                        www.bookedin.net
                    </a>
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Contact:</strong>
                    Mike Iwasiow
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Location:</strong>
                    Winnipeg (Mb), Canada
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Product:</strong>
                    A complete user-friendly web-based solution to let
                    owners of SMBs easily manage their schedule.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    <strong>ArcBees product used:</strong>
                    Gwt-Platform, Jukito,
                    Consulting services
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Testimonial:</strong>
                    <br/>
                    At BookedIN, we started using GWT-platform when the project was still in its
                    infancy. We had already started with GWT-dispatch and GWT-presenter but after
                    reviewing the code, the samples, and the direction the project was taking, we
                    decided to migrate to GWTP instead and we couldn't be happier with it. The
                    project is well-designed with just the right mix of features without making
                    the project bloated. The API is intuitive and easy-to-follow and the people
                    behind the project are very receptive to feedback. Since we started using GWTP,
                    we've been happy to see a very strong ecosystem grow around it with regular
                    activity on both the code and the discussion list. I can't recommend GWTP
                    enough.
                </p>
            </div>

            <g:Image resource="{res.imagem}" styleName="{style.imgFloatRight}"/>

            <div class="{style.sectionText}">
                <h2>IMAGEM Systèmes Médicaux</h2>

                <p>
                    <strong>Web site:</strong>
                    <a href="http://www.imagemsoft.com/" target="_blank">
                        www.imagemsoft.com
                    </a>
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Contact:</strong>
                    Jacques Gagnon
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Location:</strong>
                    Chicoutimi (Qc), Canada
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Product:</strong>
                    Software development in the field of health sciences and radiology.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    <strong>ArcBees product used:</strong>
                    Gwt-Platform
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Testimonial:</strong>
                    <br/>
                    Gwt-Platform gave us the opportunity to build reliable and powerful web
                    applications easily and quickly. The abundance of documentation available at the
                    beginning of GWT-Platform has allowed a very rapid integration into our current
                    projects.
                </p>
            </div>

            <g:Image resource="{res.blogCloudInside}" styleName="{style.imgFloatRight}"/>

            <div class="{style.sectionText}">
                <h2>Cloud Inside</h2>

                <p>
                    <strong>Web site:</strong>
                    <a href="http://www.cloud-inside.com/" target="_blank">www.cloud-inside.com</a>
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Contact:</strong>
                    Piotr Stawinski
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Location:</strong>
                    Poland
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Product:</strong>
                    Consulting and development services on cloud
                    technology
                    <br/>
                    <strong>ArcBees product used:</strong>
                    Gwt-Platform
                    <br/>
                    <strong>Testimonial:</strong>
                    <br/>
                    Once you start to create webapps using GWT, delighted by the convenience of this
                    technology you won't use anything else. This is precisely what happened in the
                    case of Cloud Inside, a polish software company. GWT is a great tool and GWTP is
                    great framework to exploit it. Choosing GWTP as a development framework
                    significantly accelerated the process of manufacturing sites, reduced the amount
                    of code and simply boosted joy of programming. Not to mention the invaluable
                    features of GWTP such as code splitting, generating content for search engine
                    crawlers, or support for nested presenters pattern.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    GWTP is a very convenient and useful framework, I recommend it to anyone who
                    does GWT programming.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 
