<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
             xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
             ui:generateFormat='com.google.gwt.i18n.rebind.format.PropertiesFormat'
             ui:generateKeys="com.google.gwt.i18n.rebind.keygen.MD5KeyGenerator"
             ui:generateLocales="en">

    <ui:with field="res" type="com.arcbees.hive.client.resource.Resources"/>

    <ui:style>
        .imageWrapper {
            display: block;
            margin: 20px auto 10px auto;
        }

        .servicesWrapper {
            width: 800px;
            min-height: 550px;
        }
    </ui:style>

    <g:HTMLPanel styleName="{res.style.blogBackground}">
        <div class="{res.style.blogLeftFull}"/>
        <div class="{res.style.blogRightFull}"/>
        <div class="{res.style.mainSection} {style.servicesWrapper}">
            <g:Image resource="{res.honeyConsultingDevelopmentSuccess}" addStyleNames="{style.imageWrapper}"/>
            <h3>CONSULTING + DEVELOPMENT = YOUR BUSINESS SUCCESS!</h3>
            <p>
                <ui:msg description="Services - Consulting + Development = your success - parag 1">Our consulting
                    services help
                    you improve the quality of your applications and the performance of
                    your
                    development team. A qualified member of ArcBees will join your team to help you with your specific
                    need,
                    be it web development, application design, tooling, or process and methodology. Our consultant will
                    be
                    easily accessible to work with you to answer all your questions. ArcBees also has the resources to
                    bring
                    your project whether it be short term or long term. We collect your requirements and we work with
                    you.
                </ui:msg>
            </p>
            <p>
                <ui:msg description="Services - Consulting + Development = your success - parag 2">On the other hand, if
                    you do not have resources to develop your idea, ArcBees can provide a complete
                    development team can build your project or cover only certain aspects of the development cycle. Our
                    expertise with advanced technology and our position as community leaders on good development
                    practices
                    ensure that your future application will exceed your expectations in terms of
                    quality,maintainability
                    and ease-of-use.
                </ui:msg>
            </p>

            <h3>PERSONALIZED TRAINING AND SUPPORT</h3>
            <p>Our team of expert communicators has been invited to conferences renowned throughout the world,including
                Google I/O in San Francisco and GTUGs in France. Their customized training sessions helped to deepen the
                understanding of GWT-Platform, AppEngine and related technologies. ArcBees also offers hands-on seminars
                on these technologies, and training with tools and processes to ensure that your development team reach
                their full potential. Introductory classes are also available for your specific needs. Contact us to
                learn benefits!
            </p>
        </div>
        <div class="{res.style.blogDown}"/>
    </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>
