<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
             xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">

    <ui:with field="res" type="com.arcbees.hive.client.resources.Resources"/>

    <ui:style>
        .sectionText {
            text-align: justify;
            margin-left: 51px;
            margin-right: 51px;
        }

        .imgFloatLeft {
            float: left;
            margin-right: 10px;
        }

        .section {
            width: 888px;
            margin-left: 34px;
            margin-right: 34px;
            margin-bottom: 41px;
            margin-top: 41px;
        }
    </ui:style>

    <g:HTMLPanel styleName="{res.style.blogBackground}">
        <div class="{res.style.blogLeftFull}"/>
        <div class="{res.style.blogRightFull}"/>

        <div class="{style.section}">
            <div class="{style.sectionText}">
                <h2>Our Hive</h2>
                <p>
                    ArcBees became a corporation in July of 2010 in order to answer
                    to a
                    growing demand of professional support for GWT-Platform.
                    Philippe,
                    the project’s instigator, initiated Christian who then
                    became the
                    main contributor to the company. Since then, he devotes
                    his
                    energies to management whereas Philippe concentrates on
                    technical
                    innovations. Only in September did Christian have the idea
                    to
                    create a new project based on the open source products from
                    ArcBees. This time, the idea is particularly aimed at answering to
                    the new needs of SMEs of a Web in constant evolution. In December
                    of 2010, Francis and David join in as partners at equal share.
                    Their role is crucial in so that to the planning and realisation of
                    this new project. Today, Christian’s idea is coming to reality: a
                    revolutionary Web application will see day in November of 2011.
                </p>

                <h2>Our mission</h2>
                <p>
                    ArcBees’ mission is to be an active and influent member of the
                    open source
                    community, while offering simple solutions and products
                    which draw
                    on cloud technologies. The company promises to make
                    available new
                    technologies for experts as well as neophytes, while
                    sharing its
                    knowledge with other developers.
                </p>

                <p>
                    ArcBees’ objectives are to:
                    <ul>
                        <li>Deliver applications which answer the highest industry quality
                            criteria;
                        </li>
                        <li>Assure clients with a pleasing experience thanks to products
                            offering the simplest interface and which only use the latest
                            technologies;
                        </li>
                        <li>Profit from the advantages of cloud technologies in order to
                            allow clients to answer automatically to demand fluctuation at
                            the lowest cost;
                        </li>
                        <li>Allow companies to migrate from their static Web sites, made
                            for PC consultation, to company WebApps optimised for different
                            devices such as mobile phones, tablets or WebTV;
                        </li>
                        <li>Encourage a rich ecosystem of developers to install a
                            diversified application market, allowing companies to personalise
                            their WebApp.
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </p>

                <p>In order to anticipate and answer to the emergent needs, offered
                    products are innovative and open the way to setting up applications
                    and services which were inaccessible or unknown to the general
                    public. In that sense, ArcBees’ innovative wallet, combined to the
                    invested efforts will rush the company towards the title of leader
                    in the Web domain.
                </p>

                <h2>Our Bees</h2>
                <g:Image resource="{res.aboutChristian}" styleName="{style.imgFloatLeft}"/>
                <h3>Christian Goudreau</h3>
                <p>In the last five years, Christian has been chef developer, for
                    different companies, of many Web applications based on cloud. He is
                    a passionate development and software engineering autodidact. His
                    implication is directly linked to the success of many open source
                    project, namely GWT-platform and Jukito. Christian has always
                    assumed a leading role academically as well as socially. He is the
                    president of Arcbees.
                </p>
                <p>In his computing studies, Christian received two excellence
                    bursaries for his academic results. He has also been at the head of
                    the entrepreneur club, of the grad committee and of Cégep
                    d’Abitibi-Téminiscamingue’s floor hockey league. Today, student at
                    Laval University, he is a program and analysis manager at the
                    Professional Administrative Staff Association of Laval University
                    (PASALU). In his functions, Christian is in charge of an important
                    data base system restructuration project. He is also involved in
                    the student-body association as Treasurer for 2011-2012. He
                    participates in Inter-University computing competitions such as the
                    CSGames. Entrepreneurship passionate, he has built two companies in
                    the field of computers and technology components which he has
                    skilfully made cost-effective.
                </p>

                <g:Image resource="{res.aboutPhilippe}" styleName="{style.imgFloatLeft}"/>
                <h3>Philippe Beaudoin</h3>
                <p>Philippe is a computing doctorate from Montreal University and
                    has been a postdoctoral researcher at the computing department of
                    British-Colombia University. His research has given way to more
                    than 15 publications, many of which have had an important impact in
                    robotics and computer animation. He also has 15 years of experience
                    in the industry having worked in the gaming business, in the field
                    of graphic hardware – where his work has given him a patent – and
                    also in the development of Web applications. He has particularly
                    intervened as chef developer on BookedIN.net, a GWT-Platform based
                    application, which is in list to be presented to Google I/O 2011’s
                    Developer Sandbox
                </p>

                <p>Very active in the world of open source, Philip has contributed
                    to the
                    development of Google Chrome and has initiated the
                    GWT-Platform and
                    Jukito projects. His success and his communicative
                    skills have
                    given him the opportunity to be invited at the
                    PrairieDevCon as
                    guest speaker, as well as at Google I/O 2011 to
                    present
                    GWT-platform. Philippe regularly keeps in touch with GWT
                    developers, allowing ArcBees products not only to be at the
                    avant-garde, but also to influence the direction of future
                    technological development. Philippe is research and development
                    vice-president at Arcbees, where his expertise allows the
                    companies’ products to stand out at a technique level.
                </p>

                <g:Image resource="{res.aboutDavid}" styleName="{style.imgFloatLeft}"/>
                <h3>David Marcotte</h3>
                <p>David has shown a strong interest in visual communication, which
                    is an important asset for every company’s success. More than his
                    training in new media creation at Université du Québec en
                    Abitibi-Téminiscamingue (UQAT), he learnt to handle different
                    graphic languages and their complex specific use, be it on the web
                    or for printing. Multidisciplinary in the heart, he is a
                    prizewinner and lends his artistic talent to different project
                    around Quebec. His expertise spreads from working with non-profit
                    organisations, young small companies such as the Cirque du Soleil –
                    for whom he was photograph of the association gala between the
                    circus and the UQUAT; association aiming at producing a
                    stereoscopic augmented reality presented simultaneously to an
                    acrobatic performance.
                </p>

                <p>For five years now, David has been working as a graphic
                    communication
                    freelancer. The devotion and relentlessness of this
                    autodidact
                    artist brings him to push the domain’s limits. Always
                    looking for
                    new imagery technology, David is actually at perfecting
                    his studies
                    at Montreal’s National Design and Animation Center by
                    taking 3D
                    design classes. Combining bidimensional and tridimensional
                    synthesis imaging to new avant-gardist technologies, David is sure
                    to give an outstanding image and an identity to any of Arcbees’
                    products. David is the Communication Vice-President.
                </p>

                <g:Image resource="{res.aboutFrancis}" styleName="{style.imgFloatLeft}"/>
                <h3>Francis Ménard</h3>
                <p>Francis has undertaken his career in online commercial sales
                    development and application development for different clients. It
                    is through his work and by a high demand that he has specialised,
                    through the years, in telecommunication project management and
                    delivery, and this, in his own consultant firm which he has managed
                    for ten years now. Autodidact, his attention to solve actual
                    company problems pushes him to always be on top of new
                    technological advances. With his consultant services, he answers to
                    an ever growing demand which allows him to deliver projects in
                    Canada and in the U.S.
                </p>

                <p>Moreover, Francis is proud of his implication in the management of Institut
                    Douceur Corporelle, a cosmetic clinic. Founded 11 years ago, this
                    company shows an annual growth of 10 to 25%, since its beginning.
                    Therefore, Francis’ expertise and dedication guaranties the
                    objectives of ArcBees to be realist. Francis is the finance
                    vice-president at ArcBees.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>

        <div class="{res.style.blogDown}"/>
        <div class="{res.style.sloganCoinGauche}"/>
        <div class="{res.style.sloganCoinDroit}"/>
    </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>
